Finding Aid for Media Resources Center (University of Michigan) films and videotapes, 1930s and 1948-1987
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Series I
  - Girls and Women, Ten part series on the changing role ans status of American women.
    - A Woman's Place 1971, 851831-I-23-4; The position of women in ancient Rome, the Middle Ages, and the eighteenth century. Features: Lynn Mattoon, UM-Philos.
      - Original:, 16mm kinescope film, neg. #108, 2-inch video #132
    - New Freedoms for Women 1971, 851831-I-23-5; Social changes over the past century that concern women. Features: Lynn Mattoon, UM-Philos.
      - Original:, 16mm kinescope film, neg. #109, 2-inch video #133
    - How the World Sees Women 1971, 851831-I-23-6; Stereotypes of women presented in a dance sequence and discussed by a panel. Features: Lynn Mattoon, UM-Philos.
      - Original:, 16mm kinescope film, neg. #110, 2-inch video #134
    - Women, Law, and Politics 1971, 851831-I-23-7; Examination of the current issues involving the freedom and rights of American women. Features: Lynn Mattoon, UM-Philos.
      - Original:, 16mm kinescope film, neg. #111, 2-inch video #135
    - Girls in School 1971, 851831-I-23-8; Stereotypes of male-female roles presented in textbooks, teachers' fixed ideas on differences between the sexes, and the subject of counseling. Features: Lynn Mattoon, UM-Philos.
      - Original:, 16mm kinescope film, neg. #112, 2-inch video #136
    - What Every Woman Knows 1971, 851831-I-23-9; Panel of women experienced in advising women regarding education and work responds to questions. Features: Lynn Mattoon, UM-Philos.
      - Original:, 16mm kinescope film, neg. #379, 2-inch video #137
    - A Woman's Work, A Woman's Life 1971, 851831-I-23-10; Six women discuss their experiences in business and personal relationships. Features: Lynn Mattoon, UM-Philos.
      - Original:, 16mm kinescope film, neg. #113, 2-inch video #138
  - Government of Michigan, Eight part series on state and local government in Michigan hosted by UM political scientist Daniel S. McHargue.
    - Administrative Agencies 1957, 851831-I-24-1; Eight part series on state and local government in Michigan hosted by UM political scientist Daniel S. McHargue. This program looks at state administrative agencies, what sort of powers they have, the sorts of jobs they do. Features: Daniel S. McHargue, UM-Pol.; John Lederle, UM-Pol.; Stanley Fontana, UM-SNR
      - Original:, 16mm kinescope film, neg. #114, Pos. #159
      - Use copy:, DVD (Box 12)
      - Streaming File:, 851831-I24-1.flv
    - Finance 1957, 851831-I-24-2; Where Michigan gets its money and how it goes about spending it is discussed by state Budget Director Frank Landers and Clarence Lock, Deputy Commissioner of Revenue. Features: Daniel McHargue, UM-Pol.; Clarence Lock; Frank M. Landers
      - Original:, 16mm kinescope film, neg. #115, Pos. #160
      - Use copy:, DVD (Box 12)
      - Streaming File:, 851831-I24-2.flv
    - Civil Service 1957, 851831-I-24-3; Civil Service in Michigan is discussed by C.J. Hess, state Deputy Director of Personnel. Features: Daniel McHargue, UM-Pol.; C.J. Hess
      - Original:, 16mm kinescope film, neg. #116, Pos. #161
      - Use copy:, DVD (Box 12)
      - Streaming File:, 851831-I24-3.flv
    - The Legislature 1957, 851831-I-24-4; Michigan Lt. Governor and Speaker of the House meet to discuss the law making process in Michigan -- how our state legislator works. Features: Daniel McHargue, UM-Pol.; Philip Hart; George Van Peursem
      - Original:, 16mm kinescope film, neg. #117, Pos. #162
      - Use copy:, DVD (Box 12)
      - Streaming File:, 851831-I24-4.flv
    - The Legislator 1957, 851831-I-24-5; State Representative Sallade and chain store lobbyist Doyle discuss the roles of lobbyist and legislator in the legislative process. Features: Daniel McHargue, UM-Pol.; George Sallade; Wilfred F. Doyle
      - Original:, 16mm kinescope film, neg. #118, Pos. #163
      - Use copy:, DVD (Box 12)
      - Streaming File:, 851831-I24-5.flv
    - The Judiciary 1957, 851831-I-24-6; Chief Justice of the Michigan Supreme Court and law professor discuss the court system in Michigan. Features: Daniel McHargue, UM-Pol.; Charles Joiner, UM-Law; John R. Dethmers
      - Original:, 16mm kinescope film, neg. #119, Pos. #164
      - Use copy:, DVD (Box 12)
      - Streaming File:, 851831-I24-6.flv
    - Local Government 1957, 851831-I-24-7; A discussion and evaluation of the various units of local government in Michigan. Features: Daniel McHargue, UM-Pol.; Arthur Bromage, UM-Pol.; Edward Connor
      - Original:, 16mm kinescope film, neg. #120, Pos. #3555
      - Use copy:, DVD (Box 12)
      - Streaming File:, 851831-I24-7.flv
    - Office of the Governor 1957, 851831-I-24-8; Governor Williams and two UM political scientists discuss the duties, functions and problems of the office of Governor. Features: Daniel McHargue, UM-Pol.; James K. Pollock, UM-Pol.; G. Mennen Williams
      - Original:, 16mm kinescope film, neg. #121, Pos. #166
      - Use copy:, DVD (Box 12)
      - Streaming File:, 851831-I24-8.flv
  - Herodotus: Father of History, Ten lectures on Herodotus and his histories by Theodore Buttrey. UM-Classics
    - From Small Causes 1980, 851831-I-26-1; Ten lectures on Herodotus and his histories. First program examines the meaning of history as Herodotus saw it in 5th century B.C. Greece, his method of interviewing people who witnessed events or knew someone who had been there. Features: Theodore Buttrey, UM-Class.
      - Original:, 1-inch video #341
    - The Way Men Behave 1980, 851831-I-27-2; Herodotus finds his role as historian, learning to give both sides of the story. Buttrey explores both myth and reality in Herodotus' Greek and Persian world. Features: Theodore Buttrey, UM-Class.
      - Original:, 1-inch video #342
    - The Story of Croesus 1980, 851831-I-27-3; How Croesus, the wealthiest man in the world, seeks immortality through continuation of blood line and reputation and then loses both. Features: Theodore Buttrey, UM-Class.
      - Original:, 2-inch video #243
    - The Rise and Fall of Cyrus 1980, 851831-I-27-4; Cyrus the Great, Persian king who conquered Cyrus and all Greek speaking residents of Asia Minor, as seen through the eyes of Herodotus. Features: Theodore Buttrey, UM-Class.
      - Original:, 1-inch video #344
    - Curious About Customs 1980, 851831-I-27-5; Herodotus was especially curious about other lands and Buttrey relates some of his best stories about the Egyptians. Features: Theodore Buttrey, UM-Class.
      - Original:, 1-inch video #345
    - Traveler's Tales 1980, 851831-I-27-6; Professor Buttrey shows Herodotus relating some of the most outlandish stories without evaluating their credibility. Features: Theodore Buttrey, UM-Class.
      - Original:, 1-inch video #346
    - The Battle of Marathon 1980, 851831-I-27-7; Looks at how the great wars began between the Persians and the Greeks. Features: Theodore Buttrey, UM-Class.
      - Original:, 1-inch video #347
    - Folly of Xerxes 1980, 851831-I-27-8; A morality tale unfolds about Xerxes, King of the Persians, trying to assume complete power over the Greeks. Features: Theodore Buttrey, UM-Class.
      - Original:, 1-inch video #348
    - Greeks Stand at Thermopylae 1980, 851831-I-27-9; Professor talks about Thermopylae and the small Spartan contingent which held off the Persian Empire. Features: Theodore Buttrey, UM-Class.
      - Original:, 1-inch video #349
    - That These Things Shall Not Be Forgotten 1980, 851831-I-27-10; The Athenian fleet destroys the Persian fleet at Salamis. Dr. Buttrey says that, for Herodotus, the facts are important, but what they tell us about human behavior is even more important. Features: Theodore Buttrey, UM-Class.
      - Original:, 1-inch video #350
    - My Friends The Philodendrons 1978, 851831-I-28-1; Twenty part series on growing and displaying plants and flowers. This program answers common questions about philodendrons. Features: Peter Kaufman, UM-Bot.
      - Original:, 1-inch video #504
  - House Botanist, Twenty part series on growing and displaying plants and flowers.
    - African Violets 1978, 851831-I-28-2; Propagating, fertilizing, using lights, and placing violets in the house are illustrated. Features: Peter Kaufman, UM-Bot.
      - Original:, 1-inch video #505
    - Ferns in the Family 1978, 851831-I-28-3; Discusses and displays tree ferns, Boston ferns, Staghorn ferns, and others. Features: Peter Kaufman, UM-Bot.
      - Original:, 1-inch video #506
    - Stuck on Cactus 1978, 851831-I-28-4; Examines the Christmas cactus and lesser known varieties. Features: Peter Kaufman, UM-Bot.
      - Original:, 1-inch video #507
    - Succulents 1978, 851831-I-28-5; Shows dividing, transplanting, and displaying succulents. Basic information and useful for the beginner. Features: Peter Kaufman, UM-Bot.
      - Original:, 1-inch video #508
    - Orchid Fancier 1978, 851831-I-28-6; Shows lovely and exotic orchids, also simpler varieties and beautiful wild ones. Features: Peter Kaufman, UM-Bot.
      - Original:, 1-inch video #509
    - Begin the Begonias 1978, 851831-I-28-7; Demonstrates cross-pollination and propagation from stems and leaves, and how the home gardener can have year-round begonias. Features: Peter Kaufman, UM-Bot.
      - Original:, 1-inch video #510
    - Geranium on My Soul 1978, 851831-I-28-8; Art and skill of growing America's most popular indoor/outdoor house plant. Features: Peter Kaufman, UM-Bot.
      - Original:, 1-inch video #511
    - Potpourri 1978, 851831-I-28-9; Exhibits and discusses unrelated plants (some beautiful, some exotic, some dangerous). Features: Peter Kaufman, UM-Bot.
      - Original:, 1-inch video #512
    - Green Giants 1978, 851831-I-28-10; Care of large house plants and the art of propagating from cuttings and air-layering. Features: Peter Kaufman, UM-Bot.
      - Original:, 1-inch video #513
    - Is There a Doctor in the House 1978, 851831-I-28-11; Explains pests and solutions for their removal. Features: Peter Kaufman, UM-Bot.
      - Original:, 1-inch video #514
    - Gone for Two Weeks 1978, 851831-I-28-12; Practical solutions for plant maintenance for times when plants are both unattended and attended. Features: Peter Kaufman, UM-Bot.
      - Original:, 1-inch video #515
    - Bravo for Bonsai 1978, 851831-I-28-13; Bonsai expert shows how the art of bonsai works. Features: Peter Kaufman, UM-Bot.
      - Original:, 1-inch video #516
    - Shape Up Plants 1978, 851831-I-28-14; Pruning outdoor and indoor plants. Tips on pruning for shape and health. Features: Peter Kaufman, UM-Bot.
      - Original:, 1-inch video #517
    - Words About Herbs 1978, 851831-I-28-15; Shows how to plant, maintain, and use an herb garden. Features: Peter Kaufman, UM-Bot.
      - Original:, 1-inch video #518
    - Wild and Tasty 1978, 851831-I-28-16; How to identify edible wild plants, and how to cook them. Features: Peter Kaufman, UM-Bot.
      - Original:, 1-inch video #519
    - Beautiful But Dangerous 1978, 851831-I-28-17; Poisonous plants are identified, both indoors and outdoors. Features: Peter Kaufman, UM-Bot.
      - Original:, 1-inch video #520
    - Getting Ready for Spring 1978, 851831-I-28-18; Explains seed catalogs and how to start plants indoors for later outdoor planting. Features: Peter Kaufman, UM-Bot.
      - Original:, 1-inch video #521
    - Dyeing Can Be Fun 1978, 851831-I-28-19; An expert demonstrates the art of dyeing with plants and flowers. Features: Peter Kaufman, UM-Bot.
      - Original:, 1-inch video #522
    - The House of the House Botanist 1978, 851831-I-28-20; Outdoor tour of Kaufman's own flower and vegetable gardens, and an explanation of how to make a compost heap. Features: Peter Kaufman, UM-Bot.
      - Original:, 1-inch video #523
  - Images of America, Fifteen part series on major ideas and events of American history.
    - Beachhead for a Nation 1963, 851831-I-29-1; This program looks at the characteristics of Puritan thinking and its contribution to the American intellectual and political heritage. Features: Charles O'Donnell, UM-Engl.; Howard Peckham, UM-Hist.
      - Original:, 16mm kinescope film, neg. #122, Pos. #1568, 2-inch video #129
    - Life, Liberty and Happiness 1963, 851831-I-29-2; Early American growth and expansion in the seventeenth and early eighteenth centuries. Examines works of Benjamin Franklin and the Declaration of Independence. Features: Charles O'Donnell, UM-Engl.; Howard Peckham, UM-Hist.
      - Original:, 16mm kinescope film, neg. #123, Pos. #1569, 2-inch video #140
    - Sugar, Tea and Taxes 1963, 851831-I-29-3; Looks at the events that contributed to the emergence of distinct American mind and outlook, and how the war for independence was a ramification of this. Features: Charles O'Donnell, UM-Engl.; Howard Peckham, UM-Hist.
      - Original:, 16mm kinescope film, neg. #124, Pos. #1508, 2-inch video #141
    - One From Many 1963, 851831-I-29-4; The compromise that framed the United States Constitution and created a single nation of 13 sovereign states. Features: Charles O'Donnell, UM-Engl.; Howard Peckham, UM-Hist.; Oscar Handlin, Harvard
      - Original:, 16mm kinescope film, neg. #125, Pos. #1509, 2-inch video #142
    - Westward to Eden 1963, 851831-I-29-5; Political developments during westward expansion in the nineteenth century, and the attempts to create a national culture. Features: Charles O'Donnell, UM-Engl.; Howard Peckham, UM-Hist.; Norton Mezvinsky; Samuel Sachs
      - Original:, 16mm kinescope film, neg. #126, Pos. #1572, 2-inch video #143
    - Search for a Soul 1963, 851831-I-29-6; Exploration of the basic ideas of the great literary works published between 1820 and the Civil War, including those by Emerson, Hawthorne, Melville, and Harriet Beecher Stowe. Features: Charles O'Donnell, UM-Engl.; Howard Peckham, UM-Hist.
      - Original:, 16mm kinescope film, neg. #127, Pos. #1582, 2-inch video #144
    - The Dividing Union 1963, 851831-I-29-7; Issues contributing to the Civil War, attempts to avoid the conflict, and the consequences of the war. Features: Charles O'Donnell, UM-Engl.; Howard Peckham, UM-Hist.; Norton Mezvinsky
      - Original:, 16mm kinescope film, neg. #128, Pos. #1583, 2-inch video #145
    - Lincoln and the War 1963, 851831-I-29-8; Examines the motivation behind Lincoln's crucial decisions during the Civil War Years. Features: Charles O'Donnell, UM-Engl.; Howard Peckham, UM-Hist.
      - Original:, 16mm kinescope film, neg. #129, Pos. #1584, 2-inch video #146
    - Boom and Brazen Years 1963, 851831-I-29-9; The rise of industry, including unions and big business, and the social movements of the day as seen by major American writers. Features: Charles O'Donnell, UM-Engl.; Howard Peckham, UM-Hist.
      - Original:, 16mm kinescope film, neg. #130, Pos. #1576, 2-inch video #147
    - Reform and the Big Stick 1963, 851831-I-29-10; Discussion of the trust busting and big stick policy days of Teddy Roosevelt, and the role of literature in the struggle to obtain true democracy. Features: Charles O'Donnell, UM-Engl.; Howard Peckham, UM-Hist.
      - Original:, 16mm kinescope film, neg. #131, Pos. #1577, 2-inch video #148
    - The Wilson Years 1963, 851831-I-29-11; Examines the domestic and foreign policies of Woodrow Wilson, his moral diplomacy, domestic reforms, and the reasons why the United States entered World War I. Features: Charles O'Donnell, UM-Engl.; Howard Peckham, UM-Hist.
      - Original:, 16mm kinescope film, neg. #132, Pos. #1516, 2-inch video #149
    - The Jazz and Exile Age 1963, 851831-I-29-12; Examines the social and political fabric of the "Roaring 20s" and the criticism of American life by writers H.L. Mencken, Sinclair Lewis, and E.E. Cummings. Features: Charles O'Donnell, UM-Engl.; Howard Peckham, UM-Hist.
      - Original:, 16mm kinescope film, neg. #133, Pos. #1564, 2-inch video #150
    - A Time of Troubles 1963, 851831-I-29-13; Examines the 1930 trend away from individualism and isolationism toward cooperative efforts to solve both the domestic and international problems. Features: Charles O'Donnell, UM-Engl.; Howard Peckham, UM-Hist.
      - Original:, 16mm kinescope film, neg. #134, Pos. #1518, 2-inch video #151
    - After the Day of Infamy 1963, 851831-I-29-14; Key events that led to U.S. involvement in World War II, important phases of the war, and the start of the nuclear age. Features: Charles O'Donnell, UM-Engl.; Howard Peckham, UM-Hist.
      - Original:, 16mm kinescope film, neg. #135, Pos. #1519, 2-inch video #152
    - Conflict and Conformity 1963, 851831-I-29-15; The growth of the nation during the post-war period, conflicts among idealists, pragmatists, isolationists, and internationalists, and the state of the arts. Guests: Richard Gardner, William Lewis, Paul Cooper, Allen Seager. Features: Charles O'Donnell, UM-Engl.; Howard Peckham, UM-Hist.
      - Original:, 16mm kinescope film, neg. #136, Pos. #1581, 2-inch video #153
  - Inquiring Mind, Fifteen part series focusing on the research and teaching of UM professors with footage from classes, seminars and laboratories.
    - A China Course 1963, 851831-I-30-1; This program features the teaching and research of UM China specialist James Crump. Features: James Crump, UM-Chinese Lang.
      - Original:, 16mm kinescope film, neg. #137, Pos. #2556
    - The Energy Analysts 1963, 851831-I-30-2; Two UM engineering professors discuss their research on liquid metals for use in nuclear reactors, and analyze their system for teaching engineers. Features: John A. Hanson, UM-Class.; David Ragone, UM-Eng.; Richard Balzhiser, UM-Eng.
      - Original:, 16mm kinescope film, neg. #138, Pos. #2572
    - Art and the Four Horsemen 1963, 851831-I-30-3; Snyder discusses his research which concerns the use of the Book of Revelations as subject matter for painting and book illustration in the Middle Ages. Features: John A. Hanson, UM-Class.; James E. Snyder, UM-Art Hist.
      - Original:, 16mm kinescope film, neg. #139, Pos. #2573
    - Maps and Mathematics 1963, 851831-I-30-4; A look at some of the ideas and technology in the field of geography and map making with a commentary by UM geographer Waldo Tobler. Features: John A. Hanson, UM-Class; Waldo Tobler, UM-Geog.
      - Original:, 16mm kinescope film, neg. #140, Pos. #2559, 2-inch video #395
    - The Study of Power 1963, 851831-I-30-5; Jacobson discusses his teaching and research as a political scientist. Features: John A. Hanson, UM-Class.; Harold Jacobson, UM-Pol. Sci.
      - Original:, 16mm kinescope film, neg. #141, Pos. #2574
    - Patterns of Heredity 1963, 851831-I-30-6; Rizki and his students discuss genetics experiments they are conducting, filmed footage from Rizki's lab on his complicated research on the genetics of fruit flies. Features: John A. Hanson, UM-Class.; Tahir Rizki, UM-Zool.
      - Original:, 16mm kinescope film, neg. #142, Pos. #2607
    - The Focus on Man 1963, 851831-I-30-7; Lurie, an anthropologist in the School of Public Health, discusses her teaching and the field work she has done among the Winnebago and Dogrib Indians. Features: John A. Hanson, UM-Class.; Nancy Lurie, UM-SPH
      - Original:, 16mm kinescope film, neg. #143, Pos. #2547
    - Reading the Heavens 1963, 851831-I-30-8; Howard discusses astronomy and a special research project involving radio telescope observations of the planet Mercury. Features: John A. Hanson, UM-Class.; William Howard, UM-Astron.
      - Original:, 16mm kinescope film, neg. #144, Pos. #2548
    - Reform In Mathematics 1963, 851831-I-30-9; Brumfield's research has centered on reforming methods for teaching arithmetic, geometry and mathematics, he discusses and illustrates the differences between the "New Math" approach and the traditional methods. Features: John A. Hanson, UM-Class.; Charles Brumfield, UM-Math.
      - Original:, 16mm kinescope film, neg. #145, Pos. #3318
    - The Painting Professor 1963, 851831-I-30-10; Lewis shows and discusses some of his paintings based on events of the American Civil War. Features: John A. Hanson, UM-Class.; William Lewis, UM-Art
      - Original:, 16mm kinescope film, neg. #146, Pos. #2550
    - The Role of Money 1963, 851831-I-30-11; UM professor of finance discusses his research into the role of banks, credit and money in the American economy. Features: John A. Hanson, UM-Class.; Thomas Gies, UM-Bus.
      - Original:, 16mm kinescope film, neg. #147, Pos. #2566
    - Records in the Rocks 1963, 851831-I-30-12; UM geologist discusses and demonstrates how scientists are uncovering the mysteries of rocks, ores, and minerals. Features: John A. Hanson, UM-Class.; William Kelly, UM-Geol.
      - Original:, 16mm kinescope film, neg. #148, Pos. #2621
    - Words of a Poet 1963, 851831-I-30-13; UM English professor and poet reads and discusses his poems and poetry and poets in general. Features: John A. Hanson, UM-Class.; Donald Hall, UM-Engl.
      - Original:, 16mm kinescope film, neg. #149, Pos. #2614
    - The Child's World 1963, 851831-I-30-14; Cutler discusses and illustrates his research into children's behavior. Features: John A. Hanson, UM-Class.; Richard Cutler, UM-Psych.
      - Original:, 16mm kinescope film, neg. #150, Pos. #2623
    - In Search of Order and Change 1963, 851831-I-30-15; Litwak explains his research on techniques for achieving orderly change. Features: John A. Hanson, UM-Class.; Eugene Litwak, UM-SW
      - Original:, 16mm kinescope film, neg. #151, Pos. #2570
  - Know Your Sports, Eight part series in which UM coaches explain the fundamentals of their sport and their coaching techniques and strategy with Athletic Director "Fritz' Crisler.
    - Golf 1955, 851831-I-31-1; This program features UM golf coach Albert Katzenmeyer. Features: H.O. "Fritz" Crisler, UM-Ath.; Albert Katzenmeyer, UM-Ath.
      - Original:, 16mm kinescope film, neg. #152, Pos. #131
      - Use copy:, DVD (Box 12)
      - Streaming File:, 851831-I31-1.flv
    - Football I 1955, 851831-I-31-2; UM football coach demonstrates two types of play series - the buck lateral and spin formations. Features: H.O. "Fritz" Crisler, UM-Ath.; Bennie Oosterbaan, UM-Ath.
      - Original:, 16mm kinescope film, neg. #153, Pos. #132
      - Use copy:, DVD (Box 12)
      - Streaming File:, 851831-I31-2.flv
    - Track 1955, 851831-I-31-3; UM track coach and track team members demonstrate fundamentals of throwing, running, jumping, and hurdling events. Features: H.O. "Fritz" Crisler, UM-Ath.; Don Canham, UM-Ath.
      - Original:, 16mm kinescope film, neg. #154, Pos. #3521
      - Use copy:, DVD (Box 12)
      - Streaming File:, 851831-I31-3.flv
    - Baseball 1955, 851831-I-31-4; UM baseball coach, using members of his team, demonstrates fundamentals of pitching and batting, compares Big Ten baseball to major league competition. Features: H.O. "Fritz" Crisler, UM-Ath.; Ray Fisher, UM-Ath.
      - Original:, 16mm kinescope film, neg. #155, Pos. #134
      - Use copy:, DVD (Box 12)
      - Streaming File:, 851831-I31-4.flv
    - Tennis 1955, 851831-I-31-5; UM tennis coach demonstrates the fundamentals of the game and discusses strategy for singles and doubles competition. Features: H.O. "Fritz" Crisler, UM-Ath.; Bill Murphy, UM-Ath.
      - Original:, 16mm kinescope film, neg. #156, Pos. #135
      - Use copy:, DVD (Box 12)
      - Streaming File:, 851831-I31-5.flv
    - Wrestling 1955, 851831-I-31-6; UM wrestling coach discusses college and Olympic wrestling and explains how the game is scored. Features: H.O. "Fritz" Crisler, UM-Ath.; Cliff Keen, UM-Ath.
      - Original:, 16mm kinescope film, neg. #157, Pos. #136
      - Use copy:, DVD (Box 12)
      - Streaming File:, 851831-I31-6.flv